{
    "subject": "Karl_Hartl",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Mozart__1955_film_",
    "human_readable": "Karl Hartl created the Mozart (1955) film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9700459241867065,
            "question": "Who created the Mozart (1955) film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.967094898223877,
            "question": "Is there a film about Mozart created by Karl Hartl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9572478532791138,
            "question": "What kind of film did Karl Hartl create in 1955?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9486321210861206,
            "question": "Did Karl Hartl create a movie about Mozart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8959343433380127,
            "question": "Who was the director of the 1955 film about Mozart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8378221392631531,
            "question": "What year was the Mozart film created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7489036321640015,
            "question": "Name a film by Karl Hartl."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7285633087158203,
            "question": "What year was the film Mozart released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7068501710891724,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Karl Hartl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6629442572593689,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Karl Hartl?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karl Hartl created the Mozart (1955) film.",
            "html": "yago_14722_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the film directed by Karl Hartl?",
            "html": "yago_14722_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Mozart released?",
            "html": "yago_14722_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film by Karl Hartl.",
            "html": "yago_14722_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14722_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of whether the information supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Karl Hartl directed the film \"Mozart\" (also known as \"The Life and Loves of Mozart\") in 1955. Therefore, the statement that Karl Hartl created the Mozart (1955) film is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}